ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials /4256
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Reprint numbers 313-374, 1971-1975. (Box 4)
  - Stability in Mensa Characteristics of Interaction Among Strangers, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Identification and Use of Creative Abilities in Scientific Organizations, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Organizational Boundaries and Inter-Organizational Conflict, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Craft Entry for Minorities: The Case of Project JUSTICE, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Supervision and Efficiency in Socialized Agriculture, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Occupational Risk Factors in Mental Health and the Impact of Role Change Experience, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - An Entrepreneurial Theory of Formal Organizations: Part I, Patterns of Formal Organizations, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Effects of Discarding Inliars When Binomial Data Are Subject to Classification Errors, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Funding the Sciences in University Departments, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Patterns of Vandalism During Civil Disorders as an Indicator of Selection of Targets, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Absentee Ownership and Management in the Black Ghetto: Social and Economic Consequences, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - An Organization-Environment Perspective on Cooperation and Conflict between Organizations in the Manpower Training System, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Psychiatric Impairment among "Middle Americans": Surveys of Work Organizations*, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Free Speech Rights of Public Employees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Worker Attitudes Toward Black Hard Core Trainees, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - The Water and May Reuther UAW Family Center, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Differences Between Physical and Social Sciences in University Graduate Departments*, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Employment Opportunities for Blacks in the Black Ghetto: The Role of White Owned Businesses, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Sex and the Single Arbitrator, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correlates of State Public Employee Bargaining Laws, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Statistical Accuracy and Practical Utility in the Use of Moderator Variables, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hospital Values, Conflicts and Supervisory Practices, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - The Influence of Collective Bargaining on Teachers' Salaries in New York State, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Employer Role in Hard-Core Trainee Success, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - The American Woman at Work, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Some Developmental Correlates of Scarcity (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Organizations for the 1980's, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - A Contingency Model fro the Dings of Problem Solving Research Programs: A Perspective on Diffusion Research, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Hospital's Value System and the Union, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sex Roles and Internal Labor Market Structures: The "Female" Semi-Professions, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Market Behavior in a Stimulated Society: Illustrating the Sociology of Economic Phenomena, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ecological Succession in Radically Changing Neighborhoods A Review of the Literature, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hospital Costs and Quality of Care: An Organizational Perspective, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hospital Technology: Prescription for Peace, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - On Administering Questionnaires in Organized Settings, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Reaction to Women's Studies, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Married Women's Name Styles and Interest in Continuing Education, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Women Going Back to Work: Preliminary Problems, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Women's Studies: Where to Now, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - The Scribes: Modern Style, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Women: Career Aspirations and Desired Family Size, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - First-Year Students Size Up Sociology, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Women at Cornell: Today, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Maternal Employment and Child Behavior, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Men, Women, and Work Satisfaction on Campus, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Coeducation and College Women, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Training of Labor Union Officials, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Local 1199, Drug and Hospital Union: An Analysis of the Normative and Institutional Orders of a Complex Organization, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - The Impact on Collective Bargaining of Equal Employment Opportunity Remedies, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Multiple Collective Bargaining A Model and Analysis of Bargaining Outcomes, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - City Government Bargaining: A Path Analysis, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Determinants of the Power of Boundary Units in an Interorganizational Bargaining Relation, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Interorganizational Dependence: A Review of the Concept and a Reexamination of the Findings of the Aston Group, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Reprint numbers 429-530, 1977-1983. (Box 5)
  - Industrial Safety and Benevolent Despotism (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Visionaries and Villains: The Politics of Designing Interorganizational Relations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Working Women: European Experience and American Need, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Quality of Work: The Views of Local Union Activists*, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Intraorganizational Mobility and Careers Perceptions Among Rank and File Employees in Different Technologies, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Methodological Issues in Quantitative Strike Analysis, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Reinstatement After Termination: Public School Teachers, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Extradepartmental Enterprise, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Organised Labour and Community Colleges*, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Uncertainty and Dependence: Two Perspectives on Environment, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Dependence on Impasse Procedures: Police and Firefighters in New York State, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Theory and Empirical Examination, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - International Guidelines for Industrial Relations: Outlook and Impact, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Strike Activity: Union Centralization and National Diversity, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Game Theory's Wartime Connections and the Study of Industrial Conflict, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - The University Labor Educator: A Marginal Occupation, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - In Support of Voluntary Employee Ownership, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Conditions Facilitating Participator-Democratic Organizations, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Conflict and the Intermetropolitan Structure of Production, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Public Sector Strikes: Legal, Ethical and Practical Considerations*, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Labor, Education, Labor Studies and the Knowledge Factor, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - The Local Union: Center of Life in the UAW, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Buying Your Job: Factors Affecting the Success or Failure of Employee Acquisition Attempts, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Centralization versus Decentralization in the Design of Human Service Delivery Systems: A Response to Gouldner's Lament*, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Power Dependence in Individual Bargaining: The Expected Utility of Influence, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Mid-Career Change in Academia: The Decision to Become an Administrator, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Relationships Between Local Union Characteristics and Worker Behavior and Attitudes, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "Union Is Power": Sketches from Women's Labor History, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - One Making the Most of Participant Observation*, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - The Acquisitive Spirit of John Mitchell, UMW President (1899-1908), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - The Election Base of National Union Executive Boards, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Compensating Wage Differentials and Public Policy: A Review, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Review of the Elusive Phenomena, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Women- Working More, Earning Less, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - The Development of an Interorganizational Control Network: The Case of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - How American Workers View Labor Unions, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Affirmative Action Programs: Have We Forgotten the First-Line Supervisor?, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Chapter The Extent of Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - The Impact of Work-Related Injuries on Wisconsin Workers, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Reflections on the Arbitrator's Responsibility to Provide a Full and Fair Hearing: How to Bite the Hands that Feed You, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Chapter 10 Public Education, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - The Costs of Defined Benefit Pension Plans and Firm Adjustments*, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - The Impact of Federal Sector Unions on Supervisors' Use of Personal Policies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Organization Set Size and Diversity People Processing Organizations and their Environments, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Chapter 8 New Approaches to Collective Power Four Working Women's Organizations, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - The Collectivist Organization: An Alternative to Rational-Bureaucratic Models*, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Employee Ownership: Implications for the Organizational Distribution of Power, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - British and American Labor Educators: A Comparative Analysis, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Predicting How Federal Managers Perceive Criteria Use for Their Promotion*, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Exit, Voice, and Silence: Consumers' and Managers' Response to Organizational Decline, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - The Quest for Enforceable Immigration Policy, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Leadership Training for Union Women in the United States: Route to Equal Opportunity, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Schools and Dollars: Fair Share for Puerto Ricans?, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Worker's Compensation Costs for Employers, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Public Service Employment in the Rural South: The Prospects for Job Transition*, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Trends in Selection and Training of International Union Staff: Implications for University and College Labor Education, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Retirement System Characteristics and Compensating Wage Differentials in the Public Sector, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - On the Empirical Testing of the Nash-Zeuthen Bargaining Solution, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Youth Employment Programs Three Southwestern Case Studies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Mediation Systems in Comparative Perspective, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Modernization Without Urbanization or Switzerland as Model Job Development Outside Large Urban Areas, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Manpower Research and Labor Economics "Special Labor Market Segments" (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - For Research to Legislation on Employee Ownership, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - The Agency Shop After Abood: No Free Ride, but What's the Fare?, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - An Empirical Test of a Leadership Contingency Model for Teaching Behavioral Science Concepts to Managers, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Professional Socialization and Attitudes Toward Collective Bargaining: An Exploration among Law Students, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Power and Tactics in Bargaining, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Economic Development A Poverty Solution for the Rural South, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Locus of Control and Career Self-Management among Nonsupervisory Employees in Industrial Settings, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Organizational Structure, Work Process, and Proposal Making in Administrative Bureaucracies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Distributional Equity in the Unemployment Insurance System, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Differentiation within the United States Capitalist Class: Workforce Size and Income Differences, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Role-Allocation Processes in Public Bureaucracies: External Political Pressures, Internal Differentiation, and the Perception of Recruitment and Promotion, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Scale Economies in Private Multi-Employer Pension Systems, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - The Role of Noneconomic Factors in Faculty Union Voting, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Unions Implementing Managerial Techniques, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Concentration Trends in Union Structure: An International Comparison, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Estimating the Narcotic Effect of the Public Sector Impasse Procedures, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - The Impact of Alienation, Meaninglessness, and Meritocracy on Supervisor and Subordinate Satisfaction, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Methodological Issues in the Use of Absence Data, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Absenteeism When Workers Have a Voice: The Case of Employee Ownership, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - A History of Job-Based Alcoholism Programs: 1900-1955, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - A Retrospective Study of Similarities and Differences between Men and Women Employees in a Job-Based Alcoholism Program from 1965-1977, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Sowing Seeds of Change: How Work Organizations in New York State Respond to Occupational Program Consultants, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - The Persistence of Ideas in the American Labor Movement: The Heritage of the 1830s, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Applied Research Studies: Job Based Alcoholism and Employee Assistance Programs, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - The Effect of Collective Bargaining on Teacher Pay: A Review of the Evidence, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Social Inventions for Solving Human Problems, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Protecting Retired Workers rom Inflation: Collective Bargaining for Retiree Benefits, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Pay Discrimination: Legal Issues and Implications for Research, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Reaching Out: New York's Hispanic Leadership Training Project, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - The Utilization Process: A Conceptual Framework and Synthesis of Empirical Findings, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Labor History Resources in the Martin P. Catherwood Library of the New York Sate School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Unions and Productivity in the Public Sector: A Study of Municipal Libraries, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Recruiter and Job Influences on Candidates for Employment, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Human Resource Planning at Corning Glass Works: A Field Study, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Fringe Benefits and Labor Mobility, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Education for Social Change: Two Routes, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - The Labor Market Impact of Federal Regulation: OHSA, ERISA, EEO, and Minimum Wage, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Organizational Behavior and Industrial Relations, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - International Trade Union Movement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Compensation, Jobs and Gender, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 102)
- Reprint numbers 531-603, 1983-1988. (Box 6)
  - Effects of Employee Flows on Utility Analysis of Human Resource Productivity Improvement Programs, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Economic Considerations in Estimating the Utility of Human Resource Productivity Improvement Programs, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Developing and Marketing Credit Programs for Specific Clienteles: Cornell University's Programming for Clerical Workers, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Resource Mobilization and the Creation of US Producer's Cooperatives, 1835-1935, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Non-Immigrant Labor Policy in the United States, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - The Swiss Experience with Foreign Workers: Lessons for the United States, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The Decline in Union Success in NLRB Representation Elections, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fringe Benefits and the Cost of Changing Jobs, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Union-Management Cooperation: A Passing Fad or Permanent Change?, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Economic Determinants of the Optimal Retirement Age: An Empirical Investigation (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Staffing: Integrating Practice with Strategy, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Decision Theory Contributions to HRM Research and Practice, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Studying Human Resource Strategy: An Approach and an Agenda, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Worker Participation in Job Safety and Health (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Labor and Politics in the 1980s, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Human Resource Planning at IBM, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Studying Organizational Culture through Rites and Ceremonials, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Labor Education: A Comparison of Cornell and Oxford Universities (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - British and American Union Standards: A Comparative Analysis (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - A Tale of Two Amendments: The Reasons Congress Added Sex to Title VII and Their Implication for the Issue of Comparable Worth, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Methods of Analysis of Illegal Immigration into the United States (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Role of Recruitment in Staffing Utility Analysis, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Mild water damage to both booklets
  - Institutional Environments and Resource Dependence: Sources of Administrative Structure in Institutions of Higher Education, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Employee Ownership: Lessons Learned (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Unionism among Professional Employees in the Private Sector, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Decision-Theoretic Utility Analysis Applied to Employee Separations and Acquisitions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Recent Trends in Collective Bargaining in the United States, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Wage Surveys: Dispelling Some Myths about the Market Wage, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Disability Benefits for Back Disorders in Workers' Compensation, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Philadelphia Story, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Human Resource Planning at IBM: A Case Study Reference Guide (only one copy), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - A Yo-Yo Model of Cooperation: Union Participation in Management at the Rath Packing Company, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - The Determinants of Strike Incidence and Severity: A Micro-Level Study, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Conflicting Statutory Purposes: Another Look at Fifty Years of NLRB Law Making, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Clerical Employees' Perceptions of Intraorganizational Career Opportunities, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Arbitral Value Judgments in Health and Safety Disputes: Management Rights over Workers' Rights, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - The Old Poor Law and the Agricultural Labor Market in Southern England: An Empirical Analysis, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - On the Uses of Social Science Research, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Ethnic Democracy and Its Ambiguities: The Cause of the Needle Trade Unions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Greasing the Squeaky Wheel: The Relative Productivity of OSHA Complaint Inspections, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Teaching about Organization Cultures: The Field Format (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Legislative Support for Multi-Employer Bargaining: The Canadian Experience, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - The Current and Future Role of Pensions in Old Age Economic Security, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - A Framework for Setting Retirement Savings Goals, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Where Have All the Unions Gone?, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Organizations and Inequality: Sources of Earnings Differences between Mate and Female Faculty, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - College Recruiting in Large Organizations: Practice, Evaluation, and Research Implications, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Rewards for Continued Work: The Economic Incentives for Postponing Retirement, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Comment on Louis Jacobson's "A Tale of Employment Decline in Two Cities: How Bad Was the Worst of Times?", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - The Effects of Variability and Risk in Selection Utility Analysis: An Empirical Comparison, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Career Transitions from Engineering to Management: Are They Predictable among Students?, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - The "Albatross" of Immigration Reform: Temporary Worker Policy in the United States (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - From Human Relations to Organizational Behavior: Reflections on the Changing Scene, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Employee Assistance and Drug Testing: Fairness and Injustice in the Workplace, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - New Measures of the Propensity to Strike during Contract Negotiations 1971-1980, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - The Social Construction of Alcohol Problems in a Union's Peer Counseling Program, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Human Resource Development and the Formulation of National Economic Policy, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Organizational Determinants of Leader Behavior and Authority, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Performance Feedback Utility in a Small Organization: Effects on Organizational Outcomes and Managerial Decision Processes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Comparable Worth: Limited Coverage and the Exacerbation of Equality, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Agricultural Machinery, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Review Symposium: The Transformation of American Industrial Relations, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Determinants of the Compensation and Mobility of School Superintendents, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Professional Careers for Women in Industrial Relations, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - The Extent of Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Aspirations to Manage: A Comparison of Engineering Students and Working Engineers, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Informal Networks and Organizational Crises: An Experimental Simulation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - How Important Are Dispositional Factors as Determinants of Job Satisfaction? Implications for Job Design and Other Personnel Programs, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Sources of Variance in Incumbent Perceptions of Job Complexity, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Accounting for the Proliferation of Two-Tier Wage Settlements in the U.S. Airline Industry 1982-1986, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Do Job Opportunities Decline with Age?, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Charges in Pension Incentives through time, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Participation by Representation: Workers or Board of Directors in the United States and Abroad, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Reprint numbers 604-674, 1989-1992. (Box 7)
  - New Developments in Profit Sharing, Gainsharing, and Employee Ownership, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Public Policies to Help Dual-Earner Families Meet the Demands of the Work World, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Relation of Age to Workplace Injuries, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Differences by Industry and Occupation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Worker Knowledge of Pension Provisions, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Employment Testing and Incentives to Learn, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Effects of Market Survey Rates Job Evaluation, and Job Gender on Job Pay, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Salaries, Salary Growth, and Promotions of Men and Women in a Large, Private Firm, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Future of Employer-Provided Pensions, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Employee Benefits in the U.S. Labor Market (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - The Impact of Government Regulation on the Labor Market: A Survey of Research Finding s, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Immigration Reform and the Urban Labor Market: Resolved and Unresolved Data Issues, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - College Grade Point Average as a Predictor of Adult Success: A Meta-Analytic Review and Some Additional Evidence, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Pensions and Older Workers, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Market Structure, Strike Activity, and Union Wage Settlements, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Toward More Valid Evaluation of Training Programs Serving the Disadvantaged, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)